Last time on Zombieland Saga, we found out we're doing a show for 500 people!
And once I realized it might bring back some memories of my past, I got super hyped about it!
But then Kotaro decided to have us train in the mountains for some reason,
and I may have gotten a little upset that everyone was focusing on survival instead of rehearsal.
But then I learned a valuable lesson when I realized that working together like that made them way more in sync as performers!
Turns out I was the one who lost my head, literally!
And just when I decided it was better to put that energy into being a good friend and working toward the future,
a truck flew by out of nowhere and knocked the hype right out of me!
What was I doing?
What is this place?
Oh, oh, oh, oh?
Ah, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Ah, oh, ah, oh.
The Spidey Elliott Laughíamosfire.
I'm so sorry.
What in the hell?
Sakura?
It looks like you finally woke up.
That's good.
Easy.
Hey, what's wrong?
You okay?
Uh-oh.
I think she lost her mind.
I can't...
Sakura!
It doesn't matter what I do.
It won't work.
There's no point in trying.
I'm all out of guesses here.
I think she's afraid of us or something.
Perhaps a slap to the face will help.
Hang on.
I might know.
You see?
Stop!
I'm not capable of anything.
What just happened?
Oh, God!
You're up.
I'm Mizuno?
In the flesh?
Wait, what are you doing here?
Look, do you remember what your name is?
Uh, my name?
It's Sakura.
Your address, your phone number, and your family?
All that?
Well, yeah, of course.
I see.
Hey, you're I from Iron Frill, aren't you?
Big fan.
Sakura.
Yes?
I can explain everything that happened to you, but you're probably not gonna like what you hear.
So please stay calm.
See, you're kind of a zombie.
What?
Come on, that's not...
Ten years back, you died. Not sure how.
No way.
What's gonna happen to her now?
I'm certain Lady Ai's doing everything she can.
Damn.
Where the hell is Shades at a time like this?
He's out.
He left this morning saying there was a business errand he needed to run.
Huh?
Well?
What's up?
Is Sakura okay?
Yeah.
Here's the thing.
Getting hit by that truck yesterday made all her real-life memories come back.
Say what?
But that's not all.
Now she doesn't remember anything that happened after she became a zombie.
Not good.
I know.
I've tried to explain some things.
I told her about us being the undead.
And about Franshushu.
Hey, these are the other girls I was telling you about before.
You mean you really don't remember our group, Sakura?
Uh, I don't...
Wait a sec.
Does this mean she can't be in the show?
The show?
Um...
It's their first solo concert for 500 people.
Huh?
It's in just a few days at a place called Arapino.
Arapino?
Yeah, it's a big deal.
A total turning point for our group.
I think I...
So you see, all of us have practiced really hard.
And you too.
I'm sure you're really confused right now.
But when the time comes, I know you'll be ready.
Wow.
Oh, I really did become an idol.
No.
You guys can do it without me.
Come on, you'll be fine.
If you practice, I bet it'll come right back.
Cool.
I'm telling you, I can't do it.
You don't know until you try.
I don't want to.
Because working for something and succeeding...
Well, I just don't have what it takes.
Have what it takes?
What's that mean?
No matter what I do, things always turn into a disaster.
It's like the world punishes me for even trying.
But...
Sorry.
Hey!
And just when she was finally coming back to her senses...
This is worse than our journey to the mountains.
Guys, am I crazy or did she just quit Franshu-shu?
Oh, no!
How have things been going?
Well, they're going.
When you first told me about your plan, I thought your damned brains must have gone rotten.
What did you call it again?
The original Zombie Village, Hezen's Highway Dream Project, or something like that?
It's called the Zombieland Saga Project.
That's the one.
Have compassion.
Act for the sake of man, right?
Yeah, Hagakure.
Great book.
But this isn't that noble.
Just keep your hands off, you giddy.
I owe a hell of a lot to that woman.
How old are you?
Hmm.
I sure had some interesting times back then.
It isn't good to dwell on the old days.
Makes you uncool.
You're one to talk.
Man, this sucks.
I can't even get into the music.
How can we during a crisis like this?
Guys, do you think Sakura's gonna forget about me forever?
Look, I know this is upsetting.
But if the rest of us don't stay strong, then the whole thing falls apart.
The show must go on.
It's not like the audience knows our problems.
Yeah, but still.
It'll be okay.
We've got to trust Sakura.
Man, I'm all gross and sweaty.
One sec.
I need to go wash off.
I'm not gonna change my mind.
But you were so worked up about it before now.
Well, what can I say?
I guess I wasn't myself.
Just forget it.
Stop being selfish.
I'll kill ya.
You're just wasting your breath at this point.
Doesn't matter how much you stomp your feet and yell at me.
I've already made my decision.
I've heard enough, smartass.
Stop it.
I said quit!
I can't sleep.
I'll listen to some nature sounds.
Hey there.
If you have something to say, just say it.
Um, well...
What's that?
I think the stars are calling me.
I'll go look at the sky.
Sakura, I can't believe you don't remember me.
You're so young.
That's right.
I'm 12 years old forever.
It's magic.
That's good.
So you'll stay cute.
Like that star thing you're holding.
Uh-huh.
You told me my star was cute before, too.
And you said you liked my smile.
I had lots of fun doing idol stuff together.
And I think you're cute, too.
Really?
What if I were the star?
Does it look good then?
You're doing it wrong.
If you're cute, those details don't matter.
But the harder I try to be cute,
the dumber and uglier I end up looking.
Because I'm a failure!
For the last time,
I'm not going to be an idol.
Well, it's time.
I suppose I must begin preparations.
Lady Sakura,
the city's best courtesan is here.
Oh, she's gone.
Where did that nerd run off to?
How troubling.
Hang on.
The mud's gone, too.
Some dogs are known to sense people's emotions.
But I don't think Romero's that clever.
Whoa!
What is this?
Some kind of zombie intervention?
They don't realize it,
but this is for the best.
If I stayed,
I would just ruin everything.
In third grade,
we put on a play,
and I got the lead part.
It was a lot of responsibility for a kid,
but I rehearsed the role every night in my room
until I could recite all of my lines
without making a single mistake.
Then, the day of the show,
even though I'd had all my shots,
I ended up getting sick
and had to stay home anyway.
Bad memories.
For fourth grade field day,
I got picked to be on the relay team,
so I stayed up late every night to practice
until I had the fastest time in the whole school.
But the day of the race,
I somehow managed to pull a muscle
at opening ceremonies
and had to forfeit.
Each year, I kept working hard
so I could make a comeback,
and I made relay team
in fifth and sixth grade, too.
But of course,
I always pulled a muscle
before the race ever got started.
More bad memories.
Fast forward to middle school.
All summer,
I crammed for high school entrance exams.
I wanted to erase the bad luck I'd had before,
so I tried to get into the best school
in the prefecture.
I didn't keep up with music,
TV, my friends,
or anything else I used to love.
I spent my entire middle school career
hitting the books.
And because of my hard work,
I got an A on the mock exam.
Then the real one came.
As I was leaving the hotel I had stayed at
to be closer to the testing location,
I ran into not one,
but multiple old ladies
who were having some kind of trouble.
I made it to the test in the nick of time,
but I was all frazzled during the exam
and kept making mistakes.
So I didn't get into my top school.
One of the worst memories.
Everything I can remember is awful.
They don't understand.
Even if that one girl
is the real Ai Mizuno.
There's no way
I'll ever become an idol.
It's such a waste
that you're not in a club.
I mean,
you're really good at sports
and physical stuff like that.
Look,
I told you I'm finished.
I might as well not bother.
The harder I try,
the worse everything seems to turn out.
I just don't have what it takes,
so it's better if I don't try at all.
I don't know.
I guess it's because
I've never really thought of mistakes
or failures as being a bad thing.
They always end up helping me
with whatever happens next.
And if I want to be the best version of me,
then I'll just have to find a way
to overcome any hurdles, you know?
I guess it's because
I've never really thought of mistakes
or failures as being a bad thing.
I was trying my best.
And just when I thought
my bad luck would change,
I died and came back as a zombie.
Am I cursed or something?
Hey, what are you doing out so late,
young lady?
Are you trying to get arrested?
Because I'll arrest you.
Did you run away from home or something?
What gives, miss?
What's the difference?
All right.
Come with me to...
Not again!
You know damn well
this isn't where you need to be.
Right, Sakura?
Uh...
And you are...
KOTORO TATSUMI, DUMMY!
I'm sorry.
What are you trying to show me?
Nijino Matsubara.
Yeah, I know.
The forest.
But it's too dark out to see anything.
That's you right now.
Huh?
There are bright points all around you.
Saga may be small,
but there's a person for every light you see.
Uh...
What are you getting at here?
Just like they're waiting for the sun to rise over Nijino Matsubara,
there are people out there waiting for you to shine as an idol.
Two or three at least.
Just do your concert without me, okay?
I'm sure it'll be much better if I stay far away from it.
And I know I don't have what it takes.
So, you really don't want to be an idol then?
Can you look into my eyes and tell me that honestly?
Back then...
I want to be just like Ai.
She's so strong and confident.
All right, make some noise!
Woo!
I wonder if I'll ever shine as bright as her.
This is it!
I'm gonna try one more time!
I can't be afraid to give it my best!
And look at how well that turned out.
I should have known I'd fail at that just like everything else.
That the best choice was to give in.
But I was stupid and got my hopes up about being an idol.
So I rushed out of the house earlier than usual.
And then boom, dead.
That's just who I am.
But you came back to life as an idol who can save Saga.
What makes you think that'll happen?
And why me?
I mean, I never asked to become a zombie!
One day you'll understand all of those things.
Don't give me hope!
Hope is what got me killed in the first place!
How bad can one person's luck be?
If you want to do this idol thing, then go right ahead!
But leave me out of it!
I just...
Don't want to be dragged into this, okay?
Well, alright.
Then go wherever you want.
If you're determined to spend your life this way...
Afterlife, whatever!
Then please, don't let me stop you!
I know I'm doomed.
You didn't have to rub it in.
If I had had any choice in the matter, I would have never come back in the first place.
Did you miss me?
Aw, come on!
Did you really think I'd let your little pity party go on all night long?
Get lost!
You don't know anything!
It's not like you've died before!
You don't know how I feel!
I have what it takes!
Whether or not you have what it takes is irrelevant, because I do!
Got it?
And what it takes is good stuff!
Good stuff that I definitely have, alright?
Listen to me!
I will never, and I mean never abandon you!
Sakura here. Why are they bugging me when they know I can't do it? How can I go on with life if I'm dead?
Next time on Zombieland Saga, Episode 12, Good Morning Again Saga. What does it all mean?